Gabrielle Giffords Papers, 1995-2012 (bulk 2007-2012)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: Congressional Activities, 1995-2012
  - Series 2: Legislative Activity Files, 2007-2012
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2009 requests (2 of 2), 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2010 requests (1 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2010 requests (2 of 2), 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2010 requests, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2011 requests (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2011 requests (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2011 requests, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Appropriations Committee- Fiscal Year 2012 requests, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Appropriations Committee- Requests binder, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Appropriations Committee- Transportation requests (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Appropriations Committee- Transportation requests (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Arizona Healthcare concerns, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Arizona Judiciary issues, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Auto Bailout, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Banking and Finances, 2006-2010 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bipartisan Tax Fairness and Simplification Act, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Blue Dog budget principles, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Blue Dog Coalition, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Blue Dog Coalition, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Border, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Border cell tower, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Border checkpoint (1 of 4), 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Border checkpoint (2 of 4), 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Border checkpoint (3 of 4), 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Border checkpoint (4 of 4), 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Border checkpoints, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Border checkpoints, 2007-2010 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Border crossing environmental impact, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Border fence, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Border security (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Border security (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Border security (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Border security (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Border Security and Immigration briefing book, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Border Security Accountability Act, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Car dealerships, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Coalition for a Safe and Secure Border, District of Columbia briefings (1 of 2), November, 2009-December, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Coalition for a Safe and Secure Border, District of Columbia briefings (2 of 2), November, 2009-December, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Combat Troops Tax Relief Act, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Community Workgroup on Southern Arizona Checkpoints final report (1 of 2), August 21, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Community Workgroup on Southern Arizona Checkpoints final report (2 of 2), August 21, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Community Workgroup on Southern Arizona Checkpoints final report, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Congressional Record Statements, 2007-2010 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Congressional report, August, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Co-Sponsor solicitation letters, 2007-2010 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-F (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-F (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-F (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-G (1 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-G (2 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" A-G (3 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" G-Z (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" G-Z (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" G-Z (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" H-Z (1 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" H-Z (2 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, "Dear Colleague" H-Z (3 of 3), 2009-2010 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Critical Path partnerships, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Defense, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Steering and Policy Committee, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Domestic Manufacturing and Energy Jobs Act, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Drugs in America, 2009-2010 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Earmark reform, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Economic report presentations, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Economic stimulus, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Education, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Ed Board briefing book, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Ed Board/End of Year, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - El Rio Health Center, 2007 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Electronic medical records, 2006-2007 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Energy Generation Choices and Interconnection Act, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Energy Legislation, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Environment, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Executive Compensation limitations, 2009 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - E-Verify Bill (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - E-Verify Bill (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - E-Verify Bill (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - E-Verify Bill (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - E-Verify Bill (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Family and Medical Leave Act, 2007-2008 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Financial literary, 2008 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - First Term report, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal responsibility, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - General healthcare (1 of 5), 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - General healthcare (2 of 5), 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - General healthcare (3 of 5), 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - General healthcare (4 of 5), 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - General healthcare (5 of 5), 2007-2009 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Government Accountability Office checkpoint report, August, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Green Valley water, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Gun policies, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - H-1B visa reform (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - H-1B visa reform (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - H-1B visa reform (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Healthcare and Medicaid, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Healthcare reform briefing book, 2009 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Healthcare reform briefing book, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Healthcare reform presentations and notes (1 of 2), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Healthcare reform presentations and notes (2 of 2), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Hoover Power Plant Act, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - H.Con.Res. 49- Local Radio Freedom Act, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 22- United States Postal Service, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 648- No Child Left Behind Improvements Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 690- Amend title 10, United States Code, to reduce the minimum age for receipt of military retired pay, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 715- Saguaro National Park Boundary Expansion and Study Act, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 800- Employee Free Choice Act, 2007-2009 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 847- James Zadroga 9/11 Health and Compensation Act, 2010 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 914- Physician Workforce and Graduate Medical Education Enhancement Act, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 1018- Restore Our American Mustangs Act, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 1228- Teaching Geography is Fundamental Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 1249- America Invents Act, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 1495- Water Resources Development Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 1835- New Alternative Transportation to Give Americans Solutions (NAT GAS), 2010 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 1885- Santa Cruz Valley National Heritage Area Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 1908- Patent Reform Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - H.R. 1992- Decent Working Conditions and Fair Competition Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - H.R. 2262- Hardrock Mining and Reclamation Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - H.R. 2509- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (1 of 3), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - H.R. 2509- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (2 of 3), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - H.R. 2509- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (3 of 3), 2009 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - H.R. 2592- Safe and Effective Drug Development Act, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - H.R. 3081- Continuing Appropriations Act, 2011 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - H.R. 3162- Children's Health and Medicare Protection Act (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - H.R. 3162- Children's Health and Medicare Protection Act (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - H.R. 3287- Tumacacori Highlands Wilderness Act (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - H.R. 3287- Tumacacori Highlands Wilderness Act (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - H.R. 3301- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - H.R. 3301- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - H.R. 3301- Southeast Arizona Land Exchange and Conservation Act (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - H.R. 3328- Sierra Vista Subwatershed Feasibility Study Act, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - H.R. 3648- Mortgage Forgiveness Debt Relief Act, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - H.R. 3962- Affordable Healthcare for America Act, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - H.R. 3962- Affordable Healthcare for America Act briefing book, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - H.R. 3997- Heroes Earning Assistance and Relief Tax Act, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - H.R. 4040- Consumer Product Safety Modernization Act, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - H.R. 4088- Secure America through Verification and Enforcement Act, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - H.R. 4213- American Jobs and Closing Tax Loopholes Act, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - H.R. 4486- Amend the Internal Revenue Code of 1986 to treat distributions of debt securities in a tax free spin-off transaction in the same manner as distributions of cash or other property, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - H.R. 4495- Jim Kolbe Post Office, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - H.R. 5034- Comprehensive Alcohol Regulatory Effectiveness Act, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - H.R. 5307- Ultralight Smuggling Prevention Act voting slip, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - H.R. 5883- Renewable Energy Jobs and Security, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Housing, 2007-2009 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Housing, 2010 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Housing and Foreclosure, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Immigration, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Immigration, 2009-2010 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Immigration and Customs Enforcement legislation, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Immigration Health Reimbursement, 2008-2009 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Immigration Reform (1 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Immigration Reform (2 of 2), 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Immigration Reform (1 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Immigration Reform (2 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Immigration Reform (3 of 3), 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Indian affairs, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Indian Healthcare and Education, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Insurance, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Iraq talking points, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Iraq Troop Escalation, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Labor Unions, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Long-Term Acute Care, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Marijuana Policy Project Mason-Dixon Poll in A208, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Member pay cut legislation, 2006-2010 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Mental health, 2007-2008 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Military Community Relations Committee- Davis-Monthan Air Force Base concerns, 2006-2008 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Military issues (1 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Military issues (2 of 2), 2008-2010 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Motorcycle Caucus, 2007-2009 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - National Active & Retired Federal Employees Association legislation, 2009-2010 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - National Guard and Reserve Soft Landing Reintegration Act, 2009 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - National School Boards Association, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Natural Gas Act, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Navajo Nation Trust litigation issues, February, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Net neutrality, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Notes (1 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Notes (2 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Notes (3 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Notes (4 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Notes (5 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Notes (6 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Notes (7 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Notes (8 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Notes (9 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Notes (10 of 10), ca. 2007-ca. 2010 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Operation Jump Start, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Operation Streamline, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Position statements, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Position statements, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Position statements, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Pro Health reform, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Public Health Service egg donor registry, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Real Estate, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Renewable Energy Assistance Act, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Rosemont Copper Mine (1 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Rosemont Copper Mine (2 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Rosemont Copper Mine (3 of 3), 2009-2011 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Rural Broadband Deployment, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Rural Healthcare Coalition, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - San Pedro Watershed, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Security through Regularized Immigration and a Vibrant Economy Act, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Selected Reserve Continuum of Care Act, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Shooting Range Expansion Act, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Sirius/XM radio merger, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Small Business legislation, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Solar Tax Package, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Solar Uniting Neighborhoods Act, 2010 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - State of Arizona Homeland Security Coordinating Council (1 of 2), December 12, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - State of Arizona Homeland Security Coordinating Council (2 of 2), December 12, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - State Criminal Alien Assistance Program, 2008-2009 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - State of the District briefing, April 11, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - State of the District prep materials, April 11, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Stored Value Device Registration and Reporting Act, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Subprime mortgages, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Survivor Benefit Plan special needs trust, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Taxes, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Technology CEO Council, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Telecommunications, 2007-2010 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Television white space, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Trade, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Transportation and Infrastructure, 2007-2010 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Tribal Issues Dear Colleague letters, 2009-2010 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Tucson Sector Checkpoints, 2009 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - United States Army Corps of Engineers, 2007-2008 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - United States Postal Service, 2007-2010 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Upper San Pedro Partnership, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Veteran Support, 2008-2010 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Women's Health, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Yuma Courthouse Project, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Series 3: Issue Files, 2005-2011
    This series contains research on specific topics and issues primarily related to the region such as energy, Davis-Monthan Air Force Base, Native Americans, Rosemont Mine as well as healthcare and education. It is arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - Agriculture, 2007-2010 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Animals, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Arizona education, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Arizona renewable energy, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Arizona Solar, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Arizona Transportation Requests, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Arizona Water, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Base Realignment and Closure, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Biotech, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Bridges, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of Land Management Solar Management, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Business reform, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Cancer, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Children's Health, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Credit Unions, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base, 2009-2011 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base encroachment, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base F-35, 2009-2010 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Davis-Monthan Air Force Base renewable energy, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Defense Language Transformation Roadmap, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Dental health, 2005 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Drug importation, August 15, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Electric vehicles, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Electricity, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Federal Detention Center, San Xavier District, Tohono O'odham Nation, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency Mapping Project, Santa Cruz County, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Fort Huachuca, 2008-2010 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - General Business, 2006-2007 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - General health (1 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - General health (2 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - General health (3 of 3), 2006-2008 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - General military, 2008-2010 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Headstart, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Healthcare, 2007-2008 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Huachuca City, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Identity theft, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Indian affairs, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Indian Health Service, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Indian mining, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Intertribal Council of Arizona, 2008-2009 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Intertribal Council of Arizona/Arizona Indian Gaming Association Congressional Week, April 27, 2010-April 29, 2010 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Intertribal Council of Arizona/Arizona Indian Gaming Association Congressional Week, March 29, 2011-March 31, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Judiciary, 2009-2010 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Labor unions (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Labor unions (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Libraries, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Medicare (1 of 3), 2008-2010 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Medicare (2 of 3), 2008-2010 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Medicare (3 of 3), 2008-2010 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Mental health, 2011 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Military and Renewables, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Military health, 2006-2010 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - National Congress of American Indians, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Natinoal Security Personnel System, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Navajo Generating Station, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - No Child Left Behind Act (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - No Child Left Behind Act (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Optometry, 2007-2009 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Payday lending, 2007-2010 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Physical therapy, 2007-2008 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Prison, 2007-2011 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Psychiatry, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Radiology, 2009 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Respiratory health, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Rosemont Copper Project (1 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Rosemont Copper Project (2 of 2), 2007-2010 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - San Carlos Apache, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - San Pedro River Valley I-10 Bypass Expressway, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Santa Cruz River, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Santa Cruz Watershed, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Seniors, 2008-2011 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Small Businesses, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Social Security, 2007-2009 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Solar, 2008-2010 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Taxes, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Transportation, 2007-2011 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Tucson Tower, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - University of Arizona, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Utilities, 2009-2010 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Venture Capital and Clean Energy, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Veterans, 2006-2009 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Women's health, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Yavapai-Apache Nation, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Series 4: Voting Records, 2008-2010
    This series contains guides outlining her legislative activities and vote ratings.
    - Legislative Activity Guide, 111th Congress, 1st session, January, 2009-June, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Legislative Activity Guide, 111th Congress, 1st session, January, 2009-December, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Legislative Activity Guide, 111th Congress, 2nd session, January, 2010-June, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Senior voting record, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Vote ratings, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Series 5: Speeches, 2007-2011
    This series contains the speeches given by Giffords for various events. It is arranged chronologically.
    - January, 2007-February, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - March, 2007-April, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - May, 2007-June, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - July, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - August, 2007-September, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - October, 2007-November, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - December, 2007-January, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - February, 2008-March, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - April, 2008-July, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - August, 2008-September, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - December, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 2009 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 2010 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 2011 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Series 6: Correspondence, 2006-2012
    This series contains invitations to events, congratulatory letters and cards, form letters, letters with other officials and from constituents.
    - Subseries 1: Acknowledgement and Invitations, 2007-2012
      This subseries contains invitations to events as well as thank you and congratulatory letters and cards. Also included are Giffords outgoing congratulatory letters. It is arranged alphabetically.
      - Giffords Outgoing (1 of 5), 2007-2012 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Giffords Outgoing (2 of 5), 2007-2012 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Giffords Outgoing (3 of 5), 2007-2012 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Giffords Outgoing (4 of 5), 2007-2012 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Giffords Outgoing (5 of 5), 2007-2012 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Happy Birthday, 2007-2011 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Kudos (1 of 2), 2006-2012 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Kudos (2 of 2), 2006-2012 (Box 33, Folder 13)